Guide to the Abe Burrows papers, 1904-1993
The New York Public Library. Billy Rose Theatre Division.
- Series XIII: Oversized Visual, 1942-1991; 589777; 5 boxes and 3 map case size folders
  - Poster for Happy Hunting, 1956; 589812; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Poster for How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying, in French, n.d.; 589813; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Poster for No Hard Feelings, 1973; 589814; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - Poster for Reclining Figure, 1954; 589815; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - Poster for Say, Darling, 1958; 589816; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Poster for Silk Stockings, 1955; 589817; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Poster for Three Wishes for Jamie, 1952; 589818; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - Poster for Two on the Aisle, 1951; 589819; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - Poster for What Makes Sammy Run?, 1964; 589820; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 17)
  - Drama Critic's Circle Award for How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying, 1961-1962; 589821; 1 folder (Map-case 1, Folder 1)
  - Mounted playbills for: Guys and Dolls, Can-Can, Reclining Figure, and How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying, 1950-1961; 589822; 1 folder (Map-case 1, Folder 2)
  - Advertising poster for Abe Burrows Show, 1948; 589823; 1 folder (Map-case 1, Folder 3)